

MSc. Lukáš Buňát









🎮 Full-Stack Developer 🖥 Big Data Engineer 🖓 Business Consultant



+420 731 277 533



bunat.cz



bunatl



lukasbunat

Full-Stack Developer with the primary focus on front-end with 4+ years of experience in web/software development and data science. I have an educational background in Computer Science and Business Informatics at many different universities all over the world. I thrive on multicultural teams and enjoy resolving everyday challenges using my analytical thinking and problem-solving skills.



Technical Skills

	Front-End	React.js 16.12, JavaScript ES6/2017, TypeScript, HTML5, CSS3, Sass		
Full-Stack	Back-End	AWS services, serverless, Node.js, express.js, apache2, nginx		
technologies	Database	MongoDB (Mongoose, Monk), DynamoDB, MySQL, MS SQL Server, lowdb		
_	Other	Yarn, npm, webpack, parcel, react testing library, Jest, Cypress, postman		
Data Science	Python, SQL SSIS/SSAS, BI, Tableau, Hadoop, PySpark, Rapid Miner, Hive, Spark, Jupyter			
Collaboration	GIT (GitHub), JIRA, Trello, Slack, Asana, G Suite, MS Teams, Office 365			



Work Experience



- Senior React developer delivering full-stack & mobile application for medium/large-size Czech companies
- Consulting clients in data warehousing manners

Web dev, tutor & consultant 05/2015 - 08/2021 **Freelance** Prague, Czech Republic

- Consult businesses, to digitalize their processes
- Building (web) automatization tools
- Build and maintain business React/WordPress websites
- Tutor university students in programming & math
- Implementing additional web apps' functionalities

Video services specialist 05/2018-05/2019 O2 Czech Republic a.s. Prague, Czech Republic

- I helped to deliver the O2TV platform with 500K users
- **O2TV** is a content streaming platform built with ReactJS and supported with other JAVA SE/EE & C applications
- I integrated an audio/video player for Prague's city hall

Big Data Analyst 10/2017 - 12/2017 **Comillas Pontifical University** Madrid, Spain

- Analyzed Spain's power distribution system to discover consumption patterns using clustering techniques
- Analyzed data were stored in **Hadoop**, I processed them with Spark (for faster processing) and I used Hive for SQL-like interface. Code is written in PySpark
- The findings (visualized in pandas) allowed to pre-assign the necessary resources in each range of time or season



Featured Projects

Portalo

- Portalo is a portal that links internal and external web apps into a single portal. Users' module allows manage employees and their information stored in a database
- I created this project as part of my diploma thesis and distributed it as an open-source code
- Front-end part is written in ReactJS with Ant Design and back-end using GraphQL with DynamoDB, Lambda, IAM, Amplify and Cognito services. Hosted on AWS.

EconMetrics CZ

- The application provides company profiling, economical scoring and other multicriteria analysis using gathered and structured available public data
- Reports from EconMetrics can be used either by individuals or companies
- API enables automatization for 3rd parties
- Currently is project in development

Company Business Intelligence Analysis

- I designed and created a database in MS SQL Server based on the structure of the given raw data
- With data pumps I imported raw data from excel, txt, csv and MS Access files, using ETL operations in SQL SSIS
- Based on stored data, I built OLAP cube in SQL SSAS and graphically represented them in Tableau

From 2014 to 2019 I had been working as a volunteer tutor at international student club at CTU.





New creative and innovative approaches to problem solving



Very good (cross-culture) communication for constructive teamwork



Enthusiastic and passionate about learning new things and technologies



Decisiveness and good decision-making (even uder pressure) & leadership



Effective time managment to ensure tasks' deadlines are met



Education

Unive	rsity, Year(s) of Study	Field of study, Faculty	Location
SE TO	University of Economics and Business	Information systems and technologies MSc. Graduate (Ing.)	Prague,
PRAZE	2019 - 2021	Faculty of informatics and statistics	▼ Czech Republic
	Czech Technical University	Open Informatics	Prague,
	2019	Faculty of Electrical Engineering	Czech Republic
(all)	University of Finance and	Applied Informatics	Duague
(18 18)	Administration	Undergraduate (Bc.)	Prague, Czech Republic
	2018-2019	Faculty of Economics	Czecii Kepublic
REE	Czech Technical University	Information Systems and Management	Prague, Czech Republic
	2014–2018	Faculty of Information Technology	
STATIONAL PROPERTY OF THE PROP	Kyungpook National University	Exchange studies	Daegu,
A CONTRACTOR OF THE PARTY OF TH	2017	College of IT Engineering	▼ South Korea
AND SE	Indian Institute of Technology Madras	Exchange studies	Chennai,
E III. Michael and St.	2016	Department of Computer Science	▼ India
A MAN A COLOR	Delft University of Technology	Case study of Earthquakes in Netherland	Delft,
Tocccxu.	2016	The ATHENS Programme	Netherlands
A	Mayflower College of English	Summer language school	Plymouth, United
	2012		Kingdom



Certificates



CISCO Academy

CCNA 1 (2013)



Autodesk





KFN of UNESCO

Cross Culture Awereness Programme